Guide to the E. L. Doctorow Papers 1931-2016 MSS.056
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series XVI. Printed Material
  - Graham, Hugh Davis and Ted Robert Gurr. Violence in America: Historical and Comparative Perspectives. New York: Bantam Books, 1969 (Box 83)
  - Dostoyevsky, Fyodor. The Possessed. New York: Signet Classic., 1962 (Box 83)
  - Doblin, Alfred. Alexanderplatz, Berlin. New York: Frederick Ungar Publishing Co., 1976 (Box 83)
  - Checkov, Anton. Plays. London: Penguin Classics., 1975 (Box 83)
  - Morrison, Toni. The Bluest Eye. New York: Washington Square Press., 1970 (Box 83)
  - Maupassant, Guy de. Bel-Ami. London: Penguin Classics., 1975 (Box 83)
  - Dostoyevsky, Fyodor. The Gambler/ Bobok/ A Nasty Story. London: Penguin Classics., 1966 (Box 83)
  - Einstein, Albert. Relativity: The Special and the General Theory. New York: Crown Publishers., 1961 (Box 86)
  - Feynman, Richard. The Character of Physical Law. Cambridge, MA: The M.I.T Press., 1965 (Box 86)
  - Wolff, Peter. Breakthroughs in Physics. New York: Signet., 1965 (Box 86)
  - Sacks, Oliver. The Man who Mistook His Wife for a Hat. New York: Harper Collins., 1990 (Box 86)
  - Einstein, Albert. The World As I See It. New York: Citadel Press., 1979 (Box 86)
  - Einstein, Albert. Out of My Later Years. Secaucus, NJ: The Citadel Press., 1956 (Box 86)
  - Bukiet, Melvin Jules (ed.). Neurotica: Jewish Writers on Sex., 1999 (Box 86)
  - March, Robert H. Physics for Poets. Chicago: Contemporary Books, INC., 1978 (Box 86)
  - Kent, Amanda and Alan Ward. Introduction to Physics. London: Usborne Publishing Ltd., 1983 (Box 86)
  - The Psychoanalytic Review. 69.4. New York: Human Sciences Press., 1982-1983 (Box 86)
  - Chomsky, Noam. Deterring Democracy. New York: Hill and Wang., 1992 (Box 86)
  - Chomsky, Noam. The Chomsky Reader. New York: Pantheon Books., 1987 (Box 86)
  - Gleick, James. Chaos: Making a New Science. New York: Viking., 1987 (Box 86)
  - Busch, Frederick. The Night Inspector. New York: Harmony Books., 1999 (Box 86)
  - Melman, Peter Charles. Landsman. New York: Counterpoint., 2007 (Box 86)
  - Bosworth, Beth. Tunneling. New York: Shaye Areheart Books., 2003 (Box 86)
  - Von Der Lippe, Angela. The Truth About Lou. New York: Counterpoint., 2006 (Box 86)
  - Halvorson, George C. Heath Care Will Not Reform Itself. New York: CRC Press., 2009 (Box 86)
  - Breytenbach, Breyten. Intimate Stranger. New York: Archipelago Books., 2004 (Box 87)
  - Breytenbach, Breyten. Mouroir. New York: Archipelago Books., 2009 (Box 87)
  - Breytenbach, Breyten. Voice Over. New York: Archipelago Books., 2009 (Box 87)
  - Shyne, Mary. "Yours Truly" and Other Stories., 1995 (Box 87)
  - Popeyemniy Mosm. Tkachenka, A.P., 1986 (Box 87)
  - Curiger, Bice. Looks et Tenebrae. New York: Portfolio., 1984 (Box 87)
  - Ruiz, Rosa Maria. Sorsalis. Buenos Aires: Torres Aguero Editor., 1994 (Box 87)
  - Chan, Roman Pina. A Guide to Mexican Archaeology. Mexico City: Minutiae Mexicana., 1978 (Box 87)
  - Ruchames, Louis. The Abolitionists. New York: Capricorn Books., 1964 (Box 87)
  - Huysman, J.K. Against Nature. Middlesex: Penguin Classics., 1959 (Box 87)
  - Kawabata, Yasunari. Snow Country. Rutland, Vermont: Charles E. Tuttle Company, INC., 1978 (Box 87)
  - Baines, Keith (ed.). Malory's Le Morte D'Arthur. New York: Mentor Classics., 1962 (Box 87)
  - Kitto, H.D.F. The Greeks. Baltimore: Penguin Books., 1951 (Box 87)
  - Bakeless, John (ed.). The Journals of Lewis and Clark. New York: Signet Classics., 1964 (Box 87)
  - Frank, Philipp. Einstein: His Life and Times. New York: De Capo Press., 1947 (Box 87)
  - Pitt, Valerie H. (ed). Dictionary of Physics. Middlesex: Penguin Books., 1977 (Box 87)
  - Kafka, Franz. The Penal Colony. New York: Schocken Books., 1961 (Box 87)
  - Kafka, Franz. The Castle. New York: Schocken Books., 1992 (Box 87)
  - Mitchell, Donald (ed.). Gustav Mahler Volume II: The Wunderhorn Years. Berkeley, CA: University of California Press., 1955 (Box 87)
  - Mitchell, Donald (ed.). Gustav Mahler Volume I: The Early Years. Berkeley, CA: University of California Press., 1995 (Box 87)
  - Yeats, W.B. (ed.). Fairy and Folk Tales of Ireland. Gerrards Cross: Colin Smythe., 1988 (Box 87)
  - Hoffman, Alice (ed.). Scribner's Best of the Fiction Workshops 1997. New York: Scribner Paperback Fiction. (Box 88)
  - Pequod. New York: New York University Press., 1996-2005 (Box 88)
  - Boulevard. Vol. 4, No. 3, Vol. 5 No.1, Vol. 5. No. 2 New York: Opojaz Inc., 1990 (Box 88)
  - Pequod. Nos. 25, 28/29/30, 33, 34., 1988-1992 (Box 88)
  - Weber Studies. 14.3. Weber State University., 1997 (Box 88)
  - Kayak. Vol. 49., 1978 (Box 88)
  - Cardozo Studies in Law and Literature.Vol.1 No.2, Vol.2 No.1., 1989-1990 (Box 88)
  - The Journal. Vol. 1. National Arts Journalism Program., 1995 (Box 88)
  - Weber Studies. Vol. 14 No 2., 1997 (Box 88)
  - The American Voice. Vols. 22, 23, 28, 29., 1991-1992 (Box 88)
  - Tar River Poetry. Vol. 33, No. 2. East Carolina University., 1994 (Box 88)
  - Raz, Hilda (ed.). Prairie Schooner. Summer. University of Nebraska Press., 2009 (Box 88)
  - McQuade, Donald and Nancy Sommers (eds.). Student Writers at Work. New York: St. Martin's Press., 1984 (Box 88)
  - Victorian Poetry. Vol. 31, No. 3. West Virginia University., 1993 (Box 88)
  - Grand Street. Vol. 6, No.1, Vol. 6, No. 3, Vol. 7, No. 2., 1986 (Box 88)
  - Omero. Vol 1, No 1., 1992 (Box 89)
  - Breytenbach, Breyten. All One Horse. Brooklyn, NY: Archipelago Books., 2008 (Box 89)
  - Praesent, Angela. Au Contraire. Germany: Erste Auflage., 1988 (Box 89)
  - Hyman, A. Sidur Chinuch Tephilah Hechodosn. New York: The Hebrew Publishing Company, 1912 (Box 89)
  - Timko, Michael and Clinton F. Oliver. Teacher's Manual for 38 Short Stories: An Introductory Anthology. New York: Alfred A. Knopf., 1968 (Box 89)
  - Dukore, Bernard T. and Daniel C. Gerould (eds.). Avant Garde Drama: A Casebook. New York: Thomas Y Crowell Company., 1976 (Box 89)
  - Brown, Stuart. Play. New York: Avery., 2009 (Box 89)
  - Piccolo, Ernesto. Morte Senza Resurrezione. Armando Scarcella., 1999 (Box 89)
  - Abraham, Pearl. Een Sterke Vrouw, Wiezal Haar Vinden?. Amsterdam: J.M. Meulenhoff., 2000 (Box 89)
  - Jergovic, Miljenko. Sarajevo Marlboro. Brookly, NY: Archipelago Books., 2004 (Box 89)
  - Pivano, Fernada. La mi Kasbah. Milan: Rusconi Libri., 1988 (Box 89)
  - Gibson, Ralph. A Propos de Mary Jane. Paris: Contrjour., 1990 (Box 89)
  - Einstein, Albert and Sigmund Freud, Isaac Asimov. Warum Krieg? Zurich: Diogenes Verlag., 1972 (Box 89)
  - Greek edition of Edgar Allan Poe, 1982 (Box 89)
  - Hoving, Thomas. False Impressions: The Hunt for Big-Time Art Fakes. New York: Simon and Schuster., 1996 (Box 89)
  - Coles, Robert. Dorothy Day: A Radical Devotion. Reading, MA: Addison-Wesley Publishing Company., 1987 (Box 89)
  - Schorske, Carl e. Fin-De-Siecle Vienna. New York: Alfred A. Knopf., 1980 (Box 89)
  - Bain, Carl E. The Norton Introduction to Literature: Drama. New York: WW. Norton and Co., 1973 (Box 89)
  - Litwack, Leon F. Trouble in Mind: Black Southerners in the Age of Jim Crow. New York: Alfred A. Knopf., 1998 (Box 90)
  - Willis, Garry. John Wayne's America. New York: Simon and Schuster., 1997 (Box 90)
  - Gatthaar, Joseph T. General Lee's Army. New York: Free Press., 2008 (Box 90)
  - Schlesinger, Jr. Arthur M. (ed). The Almanac of American History. New York: Brahall House., 1983 (Box 90)
  - Kevles, Daniel J. The Physicists. New York: Alfred A. Knopf., 1978 (Box 90)
  - Bellah, Robert N.,Richard Madsen, William M. Sullivan. The Good Society. New York: Alfred A. Knopf., 1991 (Box 90)
  - Sexton, James D (ed). Campesino: The Diary of a Guatemalan Indian. Tucson, AZ: The University of Arizona Press., 1985 (Box 90)
  - Willis, Gary. A Necessary Evil. New York: Simon and Schuster., 1999 (Box 90)
  - Taylor, William R. (ed). Inventing Times Square. New York: Russell Sage Foundation., 1991 (Box 90)
  - Herr, Michael. Dispatches. London: Picador Books., 1981 (Box 91)
  - Dickens, Charles. American Notes for General Circulation. London: Penguin Books., 1972 (Box 91)
  - Anatomy and Physiology. Volume 1. New York: Barnes and Noble Books., 1959 (Box 91)
  - Dickens, Charles. Great Expectations. Toronto: Bantam Classics., 1986 (Box 91)
  - Traven, B. The Death Ship. New York: Collier Books., 1972 (Box 91)
  - Sagan, Carl. The Dragons of Eden. New York: Ballantine Books., 1977 (Box 91)
  - Mead, Margaret. People and Places. Toronto: Bantam Books., 1970 (Box 91)
  - Angle, Paul M. The New Nation Grows. Greenwich, CT: Fawcett Publications, INC., 1960 (Box 91)
  - Birmingham, Stephen. The Rest of Us. New York: Berkeley Books., 1985 (Box 91)
  - Kinnell, Galway. Black Light. San Francisco: North Point Press., 1980 (Box 91)
  - Tranter, John. Under Berlin: New Poems -1988. St Lucia: University of Queensland Press. (Box 91)
  - Kinnell, Galway. The Past. Boston: Houghton Mifflin Company., 1985 (Box 91)
  - Cooper, Jane. Green Notebook, Winter Road. Gardiner, ME: Tilbury House., 1994 (Box 91)
  - Hall, Donald. The Bone Ring. Santa Cruz, CA: Story Line Press., 1987 (Box 91)
  - Holden, Harold. The Dialogues of Athing and Other Poems. St. Johnsbury: Inland Books., 1993 (Box 91)
  - Gheerbrant, Alain. The Incas. New York: The Orion Press., 1961 (Box 91)
  - Goldberg, Stanley. Understanding Relativity. Boston: Birkhauser., 1984 (Box 91)
  - Aronowitz, Stanley. The Knowledge Factory. Boston: Beacon Press., 2000 (Box 91)
  - Lessard, Suzannah. The Architect of Desire. New York: The Dial Press., 1996 (Box 91)
  - Zola, Emile. Nana. Middlesex: Penguin Books., 1972 (Box 91)
  - Dickens, Charles. Bleak House. New York: Signet Classics., 1964 (Box 92)
  - Dickens, Charles. A Tale of Two Cities. New York: Dell Publishing., 1978 (Box 92)
  - Walker, Alice. Meridian. New York: Washington Square Press., 1976 (Box 92)
  - Lukas, J. Anthony. Big Trouble. New York: Simon and Schuster., 1997 (Box 92)
  - Bermel, Albert. Farce: A History from Aristophanes to Woody Allen. New York: Simon and Schuster., 1982 (Box 92)
  - Alexander, Shana. Happy Days. New York: Doubleday., 1995 (Box 92)
  - Massing, Michael. The Fix. New York: Simon and Schuster., 1998 (Box 92)
  - Barker-Benfield, G.J. The Horrors of the Half-Known Life. New York: Harper and Row., 1976 (Box 92)
  - Plimpton, George. Writers at Work. New York: Viking., 1986 (Box 92)
  - Ames, Jonathan. I Pass Like Night. New York: Vintage Contemporaries., 1989 (Box 92)
  - Fitzgerald, F. Scott. This Side of Paradise. New York: Charles Scribner's Sons., 1982 (Box 92)
  - Frank, Bernhard. American Gothic. Buffalo, NY: Goldengrove Press., 1982 (Box 92)
  - Hemingway, Ernest. A Moveable Feast. New York: Charles Scribner's Sons., 1964 (Box 92)
  - Fitzgerald, F.Scott. The Great Gatsby. Oxford: Oxford University Press., 1998 (Box 92)
  - Head, Joseph and S.L. Cranston (eds.). Reincarnation. Wheaton, IL: The Theosophical Publishing House., 1968 (Box 92)
  - Will, Clifford M. Was Einstein Right? New York: Basic Books Inc., 1986 (Box 93)
  - Moore, Susanna. My Old Sweetheart. New York: Penguin Books., 1982 (Box 93)
  - Appelfeld, Aharon. Beyond Despair. New York: Fromm International., 1994 (Box 93)
  - Bloom, Harold. Kabbalah and Criticism. New York: Continuum., 1993 (Box 93)
  - The Wallace Collection Guide. London: Trustees of the Wallace Collection., 1992 (Box 93)
  - Rosenthal, David H. The Journey. New York: Persea Books., 1992 (Box 93)
  - Bentley, Eric. The Brecht Commentaries. New York: Grove Press, Inc., 1981 (Box 93)
  - Sperber, Barbara. In the Garden of Our Own Making. Watsonville, CA: Papier-Mache Press., 1995 (Box 93)
  - Kenne, John. Annotations. New York: New Directions Books., 1995 (Box 93)
  - Barthes, Roland. Mythologies. New York: Hill and Wang., 1957 (Box 93)
  - Barthes, Roland. Writing Degree Zero. New York: Hill and Wang., 1953 (Box 93)
  - Rite of Christian Initiation of Adults. United States Catholic Conference., 1974 (Box 93)
  - Nalbantian, Suzanne. Aesthetic Autobiography. New York: St. Martin's Press., 1994 (Box 93)
  - Conroy, Carol. The Beauty Wars. New York: WW. Norton and Company., 1991 (Box 93)
  - Olds, Sharon. The Unswept Room. New York: Alfred A. Knopf., 2002 (Box 93)
  - Stap, Don. Letter at the End of Winter. Orlando: University of Central Florida Press., 1987 (Box 93)
  - Ranan, Wendy. Inside Out. Pittsford, NY: State Street Press., 1982 (Box 93)
  - Ransom, Jane Reavill. Without Asking. Santa Cruz, CA: Story Press Inc., 1989 (Box 93)
  - Acker, Kathy. Blood and Guts in High School. New York: Grove Weidenfeld., 1978 (Box 93)
  - Coffey, Michael. 87 North. Minnesota: Coffee House Press., 1999 (Box 93)
  - Snodgrass, W.D. The Fuehrer Bunker. Brockport, NY: BOA Editions, Ltd., 1995 (Box 93)
  - Passos, John Dos. U.S.A. Boston: Houghton Mifflin Company., 1946 (Box 93)
  - Passos, John Dos. U.S.A. Boston: Houghton Mifflin Company., 1946 (Box 93)
  - Morris, Donald R. The Washing of the Spears. New York: Simon and Schuster., 1965 (Box 93)
  - Robertson, David. Booth. New York: Doubleday., 1998 (Box 93)
  - Scholes, Robert. The Nature of Narrative. Oxford: Oxford University Press., 1996 (Box 94)
  - Lekachman, Robert. A History of Economic Ideas. New York: McGraw Hill., 1969 (Box 94)
  - Mandel, Ernest. The Formation of the Economic Though of Karl Marx. New York: Monthly Review Press., 1971 (Box 94)
  - Christopher, Nicholas. 5 and Other Poems. New York: Penguin Books., 1995 (Box 94)
  - Bruccoli, Matthew J., Richard Layman. The New Black Mask. New York: Harcourt Brace Jovanovich., 1986 (Box 94)
  - MacBeth, George (ed.). The Penguin Book of Victorian Verse. New York: Penguin Books., 1986 (Box 94)
  - Scott, Joanna. My Parmacheene Bell. London: The Bodley Head., 1987 (Box 94)
  - Marshall, S.L.A. World War I. Boston: Houghton Mifflin Company., 1992 (Box 94)
  - Roth, Philip. The Counterlife. New York: Penguin Books., 1986 (Box 94)
  - Murry, J. Middleton. Journal of Katherine Mansfield. New York: The Echo Press., 1955 (Box 94)
  - Wachtel, Eleanor. Writers and Company. Toronto: Alfred A. Knopf., 1993 (Box 94)
  - Aitken, Robert. The Mind of Clover: Essays in Zen Buddhist Ethics. San Francisco: North Point Press., 1984 (Box 94)
  - Kahn, Si. Organizing: A Guide for Grassroots Leaders. New York: McGraw-Hill Book Company., 1982 (Box 94)
  - Faulkner, Donald W. (ed.). The Portable Malcolm Crowley. New York: Penguin Books., 1990 (Box 94)
  - Donoghue, Denis. Ferocious Alphabets. New York: Columbia University Press., 1984 (Box 94)
  - Lewin, Leonard C. Report from Iron Mountain. New York: The Free Press., 1996 (Box 94)
  - Dos Passos, John. The 42nd Parallel. New York: Signet Classics., 1979 (Box 94)
  - Melville, Herman. Billy Budd, Sailor and Other Stories. New York: Penguin Books., 1970 (Box 94)
  - Dos Passos, John. The Big Money. New York: New American Library., 1979 (Box 95)
  - Dos Passos, John. Nineteen Nineteen. New York: Signet Classics., 1979 (Box 95)
  - Melville, Herman. The Confidence-Man. New York: Penguin Books., 1990 (Box 95)
  - Sophocles, Oedipus The King. New York: Oxford University Press., 1978 (Box 95)
  - Pynchon Thomas. V. New York: Perennial Library., 1989 (Box 95)
  - Edward, Robb Ellis. The Epic of New York City: A Narrative History. New York: Old Town Books., 1966 (Box 95)
  - Lernoux, Penny. Cry of the People. New York: Double Day., 1980 (Box 95)
  - The WPA Guide to New York City. New York: Pantheon., 1982 (Box 95)
  - Mailer, Norman. The Naked and the Dead. New York: Owl Books., 1981 (Box 95)
  - Cooke, Hope. Seeing New York. Philadelphia: Temple University Press., 1995 (Box 95)
  - Cooke, Hope. Seeing New York. Philadelphia: Temple University Press., 1995 (Box 95)
  - Wolfe, Gerard R. New York: Guide to the Metropolis. New York: New York University Press., 1988 (Box 95)
  - Magarshack, David (trans). Turgenev's Literary Reminiscences. London: Minerva Press., 1968 (Box 96)
  - Braudel, Fernand. Capitalism and Material Life 1400-1800. New York: Harper Colophon Books., 1967 (Box 96)
  - Scott, Joanna. Arrogance. New York: W.W. Norton and Co., 1991 (Box 96)
  - Stern, Fritz. The Varieties of History. New York: Vintage Books., 1973 (Box 96)
  - Scott, Joanna. The Closest Possible Union. New York: Ticknor and Fields., 1988 (Box 96)
  - Havel, Vaclav. Summer Meditations. New York: Alfred A. Knopf., 1992 (Box 96)
  - Dobyns, Henry E. and Paul L. Doughty. Peru: A Cultural History. New York: Oxford University Press., 1976 (Box 96)
  - Rubinstein, Jonathan. City Police. New York: Farrar, Straus and Giroux., 1973 (Box 96)
  - Lewis, Naphtali and Meyer Reinhold. Roman Civilization. New York: Harper Tourchbooks., 1966 (Box 96)
  - Havel, Vaclav. The Art of the Impossible. New York: Alfred A. Knopf., 1997 (Box 96)
  - Holst, Gail. Road to Rembetika. Athens: Anglo-Hellenic Press., 1977 (Box 96)
  - Roth, Philip. I Married a Communist. Boston: Houghton-Mifflin., 1998 (Box 96)
  - Roth, Philip. Sabbath's Theater. Boston: Houghton-Mifflin., 1995 (Box 96)
  - Roth, Philip. Patrimony. New York: Simon and Schuster., 1991 (Box 96)
  - Kipling, Rudyard. The Light that Failed. New York: Carroll and Graf Publishers, Inc., 1986 (Box 97)
  - Gilbert, Martin. The Holocaust: A History of the Jews of Europe During the Second World War. New York: Holt, Rinehart and Winston., 1985 (Box 98)
  - Stasz, Clarice. American Dreamers. New York: St. Martin's Press., 1988 (Box 98)
  - Forbath, Peter. The River Congo. New Yyork: Harper and Row, Publishers., 1977 (Box 98)
  - Tufte, Virginia. Artful Sentences: Syntax as Style. Cheshire: Graphics Press., 2006 (Box 98)
  - Jong, Erica. Inventing Memory. New York: Harper Collins., 1997 (Box 98)
  - Kempton, Murray. Rebellions, Perversities, and Main Events. New York: Random House., 1994 (Box 98)
  - Branch, Taylor. Pillar of Fire. New York: Simon and Schuster., 1998 (Box 98)
  - Wilson, Elena (ed.). Edmund Wilson: Letters on Literature and Politics 1912-1972. New York: Farrar, Straus and Giroux., 1977 (Box 98)
  - Howe, Irving. A Margin of Hope: An Intellectual Autobiography. New York: Harcourt Brace Jovanovich, Publishers., 1982 (Box 98)
  - Clare, George. Last Waltz in Vienna. New York: Holt, Rinehart and Winston., 1980 (Box 98)
  - Andronicos, Manolis. Thessalonike Museum. Athens: Ekdotike Athenon S.A., 1993 (Box 99)
  - Bogdanovich, Peter. Who the Devil Made It. New York: Alfred A. Knopf., 1997 (Box 99)
  - Webster's Ninth New Collegiate Dictionary. Springfield: Merriam-Webster Inc., 1989 (Box 99)
  - Prescott, William H. History of the Conquest of Mexico and History of the Conquest of Peru. New York: The Modern Library., 1936 (Box 99)
  - Konrad, George. The City Builder. New York: Penguin Books., 1987 (Box 99)
  - Gallenkamp, Charles. Maya: The Riddle and Rediscovery of a Lost Civilization. New York: Penguin Books., 1981 (Box 99)
  - Maloney, Dennis (ed.). Antonio Machado: Selected Poems and Prose. Buffalo: White Pine Press., 1983 (Box 99)
  - Charney, Maurice. Comedy High and Low. New York: Oxford University Press., 1978 (Box 99)
  - Marina, William. Egalitarianism and Empire. Menlo Park: Institute for Humane Studies, Inc., 1975 (Box 99)
  - Mezey, Robert. Selected Translation 1960-1980. Kalamazoo: Westigan Review Press., 1981 (Box 99)
  - Polito, Robert. Doubles. Chicago: University of Chicago Press., 1995 (Box 99)
  - Stern, Gerald. Odd Mercy. New York: W.W. Norton and Company., 1995 (Box 99)
  - Shinder, Jason (ed.). More Light: Father and Daughter Poems. New York: Harcourt Brace and Company., 1993 (Box 99)
  - Strunk Jr., William. The Elements of Style. New York: The Macmillan Company., 1959 (Box 99)
  - Hodges, John C., Mary E. Whitten. Harbrace College Handbook. New York: Harcourt Brace Jovanovich, Inc., 1977 (Box 99)
  - Thomas, Lewis. The Lives of a Cell: Notes of a Biology Watcher. Toronto: Bantam Books., 1975 (Box 99)
  - Grimm, W.C. and J.L.C. Grimms' Fairy Tales. Hertfordshire: Wordsworth Editions Ltd., 1993 (Box 99)
  - Burton, Orville Vernon. The Age of Lincoln. New York: Hill and Wang., 2007 (Box 100)
  - Polito, Robert. Savage Art: A Biography of Jim Thompson. New York: Alfred A. Knopf., 1995 (Box 100)
  - Levin, Nora. While Messiah Tarried: Jewish Socialist Movements: 1871-1917. New York: Schocken Books., 1977 (Box 100)
  - Gwaltney, John Langston. Drylongso. New York: Random House., 1980 (Box 100)
  - Mancerson, Claude. Twilight of the Old Order. New York: Alfred A. Knopf., 1977 (Box 100)
  - Cantor, Norman F. Inventing the Middle Ages. New York: William Morrow and Company., 1991 (Box 100)
  - Shapiro, Robert. The Human Blueprint. New York: St. Martin's Press., 1991 (Box 100)
  - Kline, Morris. Mathematics and the Search for Knowledge. New York: Oxford University Press., 1985 (Box 100)
  - Gabler, Neal. Empire of Their Own: How the Jews Invented Hollywood. New York: Crown Publishers, Inc., 1988 (Box 100)
  - Middleton, Christopher (ed.). Goethe Selected Poems. Boston: Suhrkamp/ Insel Publishers., 1983 (Box 100)
  - Jersild, P.C. House of Babel. Lincoln: University of Nebraska Press., 1978 (Box 101)
  - Campbell, Mary Schmidt and Randy Martin. Artistic Citizenship: A Public Voice for the Arts.New York: Routledge., 2006 (Box 101)
  - Gruber, Inese, Frank Gruber and Donald Sheff. The World's First Quiz Almanac. New York: A&W Visual Library., 1962 (Box 101)
  - Phillips, Jayne Anne. MotherKind. New York: Alfred A. Knopf., 2000 (Box 101)
  - Phillips, Jayne Anne. Termite's Birthday, 1959., 2000 (Box 101)
  - Phillips, Jayne Anne. from Termite., 2000 (Box 101)
  - Brooks, John. The Games Players: Tales of Men and Money. New York: A Truman Talley Book., 1980 (Box 101)
  - Phillips, Jayne Anne. Machine Dreams. New York: E.P. Dutton/ Seymour Lawrence., 1984 (Box 101)
  - Sayre, Nora. Previous Convictions: A Journey through the 1950s. New Brunswick: Rutgers University Press., 1995 (Box 101)
  - Kolko, Gabriel. Century of War. New York: The New Press., 1994 (Box 101)
  - Bosworth, Beth. Tunneling. New York: Shaye Areheart Books., 2003 (Box 101)
  - Thomas, Evan. The Very Best Men. New York: Simon and Schuster., 1995 (Box 101)
  - Foucault, Michel. Discipline and Punish: The Birth of the Prison. New York: Patheon Books., 1977 (Box 101)
  - Tester, William. Darling. New York: Alfred A. Knopf., 1991 (Box 101)
  - The New English Bible: Old Testament, Library Edition. Oxford University Press and Cambridge University Press., 1970 (Box 102)
  - Judson, Horace Freeland. The Eighth Day of Creation. New York: Touchstone Books., 1979 (Box 102)
  - Lattimore, Richmond (trans.). The Four Gospels and the Revelation. New York: Farrar, Straus, Giroux., 1979 (Box 102)
  - Autodafe: The Review of the International Parliament of Writers. 1. New York: Seven Stories Press., 2000 (Box 102)
  - Shinder, Jason. Every Room We Ever Slept In. Riverdale-on-Hudson: The Sheep Meadow Press., 1993 (Box 102)
  - Fostle, D.W. The Steinway Saga. New York: Scribner., 1995 (Box 102)
  - Moliere. Don Juan and Other Plays. Oxford: Oxford University Press., 1989 (Box 102)
  - Bok, Sissela. Lying: Moral Choice in Public and Private Life. New York: Vintage Books., 1979 (Box 102)
  - Postman, Neil. Amusing Ourselves to Death. New York: Penguin Books., 1986 (Box 102)
  - Phillips, Jayne Anne. Shelter. New York: Delta Books., 1994 (Box 102)
  - Phillips, Jayne Anne. Fast Lanes. New York: E.P. Dutton/ Seymour Lawrence., 1987 (Box 102)
  - Chomsky, Noam. Keeping the Rabble in Line. Monroe: Common Courage Press., 1994 (Box 102)
  - Hofstadter, Richard and Michael Wallace (eds.). American Violence: A Documentary History. New York: Vintage Books., 1971 (Box 102)
  - Foucault, Michel. Madness and Civilization. New York: Vintage Books., 1973 (Box 102)
  - Cohen, I. Bernard. The Birth of a New Physics. New York: W.W. Norton & Co., 1985 (Box 102)
  - Mitchell, Stephen. Tao te Ching. New York: Harper Perennial., 1988 (Box 103)